yesterday evening you late at night late
at night for me
like 9:30 coming home from a meeting
with my kids school I encountered a
homeless human setting up their bed
under AM shelter ish like a entryway to
a business and had a brief encounter and
then kept on walking and there was a
piece of me that was like oh it's cold
out and I wish like I have a coat
actually I don't know the other coverage
I'm just getting that now I have like a
loveseat I know I haven't whatever
inviting them over to sleep in my in my
house and I was quickly followed by by
like are you crazy you're a
woman you have a child like that's not
not an okay thing to do what it was like
yeah no fair enough
and so that part went over of course and
I would the time the time again I'm
making that decision but if I could
trust that human if I knew that they
were safe that they were gonna commit
violence that they weren't going to
steal that they weren't going to have a
grossly damaging impact with her if they
have addictions right like that
they weren't gonna ruin my life like I
mean by me doing a good deed I would
like to do that good deed and I think it
from their point of view like if they
could get away from the elements and be
sure that they were safe truly safe like
not going to be needing to trade sex for
for shelter or whether a meals included
weather showers included whether they're
just sleeping in the garage weather like
these are spaces where you're invited to
be and yeah like so building that trust
between those two can be done with an
app that's ridiculous as that sounds
we're but the only way that could be
created is together with both of those
entities there because no one's really
signing up in a big enough number and in
order for it to be usable unless you
have a number of people
who have a bed a space to offer if you
have a number of people space to offer
who come together and say here is how I
would feel safe allowing someone to come
and use that friend for the night and
the other side is you have people say
you did almost people say and this is
how I would feel safe accepting that and
having that dialogue and making sure
that both parties needs are met and be
like it can only be done with a
cooperative and then they can both
utilize that application so I walk by
someone on the street and say hey I have
a bed would you would you like it do you
happen to have this like are you already
set up in this thing I only let people
who are set up in this thing stay there
or homeless people have the hub convey
on their phones and they have it's very
like they can find places that are that
are accessible to them and because
they've built a profile they've built a
foundation of trust with the community
of like yes I've stayed in these
locations and was a model guest and as
reporting goes on in it you can be able
to UM match people up so that every
person who's homeless has a space to
stay in if this if we can meet the
demand right if there's enough beds and
where there aren't enough beds finding
them and creating them and but we can
actually have a real impact and tell us
that right now they're not they're still
homeless actually sorry it's not
actually I think the homeless problem
it's ending me no roof over your head at
night problem but from that connection
from those being able to create that
community I think it's more easy like if
we've had people sleep in our houses and
met them and see that they're real human
beings with real struggles who came on
if we do more for those people and in
doing more we solve the problem so yeah
that's the kind of thing that that was
just my thought that was not like a well
thought out app that's
like yes this is something we could
create together and only together
because if you don't have yeah if a
corporation did that it would be creepy
if the government did that that would be
creepy if just the house humans did it
or just the homeless people it's not
gonna work it has to have both parties
at the table creating something together
with a big enough threat like you kind
of to of these people and two of these
people you need like hundreds of these
people haven't understand these people
or dozens and dozens whatever is you
need to be able to have that
conversation in many ways of what I need
what I need and how we make all of those
needs back and then with enough people
involved enough people wanting to end
homelessness if everyone has given money
to end homelessness in all the cities
around North America gave $5 think about
how much money that would be to create
an app with like that would overnight be
great yeah anyway we can solve these
problems we just have to come together
do it